Bob
Kazu-kun.
M-Mami-chan?!
Whatcha hiding?
Swirl
Ugh! I overreacted!
She did come over last night and all...
Does she wanna talk about that?
Swirl
Do you have a minute?
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Night and Girlfriend"
A talk, just the two of us?
Up close and personal?!
Mami-chan knows Mizuhara's
a rental girlfriend.
It's gotta be about that, right?
I heard that Chizuru-san
is a rental girlfriend.
Oh... Y-Yeah.
Huh? You don't sound surprised.
O-Oh, well, Chizuru told me what happened.
I can't possibly tell her
I saw it all go down!
I figured I should tell you that I know ASAP,
so I went to your place last night,
but you were out shopping.
I was so shocked.
I had no idea such a service existed,
and I couldn't believe you
and her were... y'know...
R-Rental going out? I was shocked, too!
Ahaha
Trash
dodge
Haha, as if!
I knew it. She's here to
yell at me, dress me down!
You tricked us all? You should
be ashamed of yourself!
Seriously? Don't you feel
empty inside when you pay?
Here she comes! The executioner from hell!
The
Silence
Sentence
Hey, tell me...
Is it my fault?
Did I drive you to this?
Bingo
Huh? She's not mad?
And wait, what?
She's been worried about that?
O-Of course not!
I-I was just curious...
Like, social research?
Really?
Yeah, yeah. Don't worry about it.
I couldn't tell her the truth,
not over my dead body.
It's too pathetic
But there is something
else I need to tell her.
Hey, uh, I'm really sorry.
I lied, and even introduced her to
all you guys, like some kind of moron.
But please, don't take it out on Mizuhara...
Wait, you haven't fallen for her, have you?
O-Oh, no.
Of course not!
I thought not! Thank goodness!
You're an innocent boy,
but I know you're not a fool.
Sorry I doubted you.
Hand...
Kazu-kun, you only live once.
You're losing out if you don't
get a girlfriend for real.
You gotta have lots of fun in college.
You won't get to as a working adult.
I don't mean to belittle Mizuhara-san's work,
but at the end of the day, it's business.
Spending your time and money
on that is a total waste.
Get it?
Y-Yeah, roger that!
That's all I wanted to say. Later.
Okay.
Sprawl
Lights
on,
nobody
home
I thought I was a goner!
But she was so nice...
I did deceive her and all...
I thought she'd chew me out.
It all pisses me off just a teensy bit.
Anyway, I gotta make sure she doesn't
find out it's still going on!
"Social research," my ass.
Lies, lies, and more lies. What a loser.
Going by how much he was panicking,
it doesn't seem to be a one-time thing.
You lie to us for a whole year
and call it "research"?
Also, that bag...
I don't know that it's hers for sure, but...
There's gotta be more to it.
Hey, Kibe-chan!
I'll cook for you tonight!
Huh? Why?
Have you been eating right lately?
I feel like you've lost weight.
You're taking on
too much work...
R-Really?
Sure,
I've
been
eating
nothing
but
instant...
But cook? Where, at my place?
Karaoke Village
Yep. It'd suck if you were malnourished.
It's not that serious.
As your girlfriend, I can't ignore it!
She wants to come over now?
Is she serious?
Okay, it's a plan! Time for shopping!
Hey, wait!
Supermarket
May Queen 2 for 80 yen
Uh, don't I get a say in this?
Someone's
having fun...
Is this gonna be okay?
It's gonna be late once all
the cooking and eating's done.
She will go home after that, right?
Not that I mind just having
dinner with a cute girl.
Nutrition
Corner
Garlic
Chives
Softshell Turtle
Avocado
Garlic
Ruka-chan?
Softshell Turtle
Huh?
Wh-What is it?
You can wait by the entrance, Kazuya-kun.
What are you planning to make?
C-Curry!
You don't need turtle for curry!
You do for some curries!
Am I not allowed to want my
boyfriend to feel better?
That's all I want. Nothing more.
Weirdly
convincing
We'll take these, please!
Ka-ching
m 0 0 l 120 0 l 120 140 l 0 140
Today's bill:
3,720 yen
(of which the turtle is 2,000 yen.)
Thanks for having me, the girlfriend, over!
L-Let me clean up the place.
Huh? Why are you locking the door?!
What if a thug waltzes in?
This area isn't that dangerous.
Hey, try to hide your displeasure!
You just sit there and watch.
You'll see how cute I am while cooking.
Okay.
Sparkle
I'm gonna do my best.
First, 200cc of water.
Tralala,
latata
3 Minute Cooking
Smooth
Get the ingredients ready.
Man, what a bizarre sight.
Look at this cute girl prancing
around my kitchen in an apron.
And she calls herself my girlfriend.
Oh, right.
Here, some pre-meal beer.
W-Wait, where did you get that?
In your fridge.
Huh, mine? Sorry.
Wait, no! This won't do!
This situation does not call for booze!
There've been too many parties lately.
I wanna give my liver some time off.
Take it
back
Oh, really?
That's too bad.
Glug, glug.
Hey, what do you think you're making?!
Some kind of drug?!
Curry! I'm making curry!
I forgot to buy cooking wine, is all.
What kind of battle is this?
Blush
Turtle Curry Recipe
Ingredients (for two)
Softshell turtle 1 bag (100g)
Chives 1
Potatoes 2
Carrot 1.5
Curry roux...
Delicious Turtle Curry
Turtle Curry Soup
Wow, turtle curry really exists, huh?
Wait, did you plan this?
Ba-dump
Were you lying when you said I'd lost weight?
Flinch
Uh, who can say?
Maybe I just gained weight myself.
Shoo Shoo
Anyway, leave me alone!
I'll stab you
Whatever the reason,
she's doing all this for me.
I should be grateful, really.
So this is how it feels.
How what feels?
I've never fallen in love before...
TIL how it feels to cook
a meal for your boyfriend.
Here. Eat up.
Thanks.
Huh? Wow, this is super yummy!
Really? Yay!
I can't believe how good it tastes!
Even though
you poured in
all that beer
Eat all you want.
Will you be able to recover?
What's gonna happen next?
Too
close...
Self-loathing
We went shopping, ate dinner together,
and now we're watching a TV show...
and there's no cash involved.
And normally, she'd stay over,
and we'd have sex a couple times.
I guess this is what it's
like to have a girlfriend.
How blessed I'd be.
If only she
were my real
girlfriend
Hmm? Texting someone?
O-Oh, don't worry about it.
Why's
she
hiding
it?
You're making this look important.
Mom
When will you be home?
I'm staying over
at Yuka's tonight
Wha?!
Hey, what are you typing?
Did that just say "staying over"?!
Tap
You're imagining things!
No, I saw that!
C'mon, what's the big deal?
I let you go on dates with Chizuru-san.
That's not the issue here!
But I'm your girlfriend.
I wanna be lovey-dovey with you, too.
Blush...
A-Anyway, you can't stay over
at a guy's place so easily!
I'll walk you!
Hey, this wasn't easy for me!
I thought long and hard about—
Wh-What the?!
Rain forever
NNE: 15km/h
Peak AP - 965 hPa
Max Wind Speed - 30m/s
Strong
Tomorrow 12PM
Midnight
Heavy Downpour Predicted
The extremely potent Typhoon 5 is now...
Smirk
Gasp
Eat up ♥
Rent-a-Girlfriend
How?
Why?
Why?! For what reason?!
Ta-da! How do I look?
Barley Tea
Cough
Wear some pants!
I left some for you, didn't I?
What? But those track pants aren't cute.
Cute or not, that's not the point!
No, that is very much the point!
I can't look at her straight!
Flutter
Besides, I never said you could stay over!
Don't bother.
Travel Info
Operation Canceled
Due to Typhoon 5, operation
of both lines is canceled.
No ETA for resumption
Please keep an eye out for further
typhoon and train info...
The trains have stopped running.
I know you're not the kind of guy who'd
throw a girl out on her own in this rain.
Are you kidding me?
You sly...
I have to spend a whole night
together with this cute thing?
This is too much for me to handle!
And you know...
Keep it down.
Huh? Weally?
The girl next door will hear you.
You meanie! You're thinking
about Chizuru-san, even now!
Do I mean nothing to you?!
I-I just meant not to bother the neighbors!
If Mizuhara found out I let
Ruka-chan stay the night...
What's all this now? Didn't you
say you couldn't go out with her?
Menacing
Are you just messing around? Is that why
you let her stay the night, playboy?
The one thing
I don't want
happening...
I get it.
Jeez, fine.
I'm one step ahead of her, just by
getting to spending the night with you.
I'll obey the tenant here.
I swear!
Ah!!
Seriously, stop it!
Squeeze
I mean it!
Tap
I get it, I get it!
Hell, even now...
I'm copping all kinds of feels!
Sheesh, fine.
That's dangerous in its own right!
Relax. I won't jump you or anything.
But you fed me turtle, an aphrodisiac!
You're obviously
out for the kill!!
I mean, I would love nothing more
than for you to make a move,
but just by getting to stay over,
I've fulfilled one of my goals.
Get it?!
Ah!!
Squeeze
Tap
Sheesh, what she says and what she
does are completely different!
I give up!
Anyway,
wear some pants!!
Anyway, wear some pants!
Oh, okay, okay.
I'll sleep in
the kitchen!
Stay away!
Okay, okay!
Once is
enough!
Once is enough!
And keep
it down!
I'm gonna take a shower!
I'm sweating buckets!
Have fun, honey.
Even the strands
of hair by the drain are
too stimulating for me...
Can I really make it through this night?
Ruka-chan can say whatever she likes,
but who knows what she's planning?
If we were actually a couple,
we'd have already...
Hard
Damn thing
has zero
integrity
Maybe I should rub one out.
Oh, Kazuya-kun, want some hot milk?
Sparkle
I made some
thinking you'd be
out soon.
Aren't I just perfect?
Oh, sure.
Did you... do something in the shower?
ba-dump
N-Nothing!
Drink
Gulp Gulp
Slurp...
He so
did...
What's going on?
I was just surprised by how
many views it was getting.
Whoa, 80,000 likes? Amazing!
I just recorded it with
a friend for the heck of it,
and it seems the algorithm started pushing it.
It's gotta be 'cause she's cute!
An influencer
with 80k likes,
right here...
It's a mandate from the masses!
Well, yeah.
There aren't many girls as cute as her around.
Ruka-chan always dresses up when we meet,
People are so dumb...
so I've never seen her in such casual wear.
She's exposing her cleavage,
and her skin's all flushed...
I wanna cop a feel!
And I never realized it before,
but she's so fair... and sexy.
So this is what Ruka-chan's really like.
Oh, yeah.
Wanna see the pic I took with a friend?
Condoms...
Drip
Those were totally condoms right there!
Why does Ruka-chan have those?!
Holy crap... What's going on here?!
This is so awkward!
Time has come to a standstill for us!
P-Please pretend you didn't see that.
It was just...
Just in case.
Kazuya
I'm going to sleep!
I can't take any more of this!
Sparkle
A
h
a
Sparkle Sparkle
30 minutes
have passed...
Man, I can't even sleep.
Torment
Did Ruka-chan fall asleep?
I'm so glad I rubbed one out in the shower.
If not for the post-nut clarity,
who knows what I would've done?
But anyway, what's gotten into Ruka-chan?
She's too aggressive tonight.
Maybe I'm stressing her out
too much due to Mizuhara...
TIL how it feels to cook a
meal for your boyfriend.
OOMPH
Rub
What?
I feel something touching my back!
Touch                  Touch
The breeze? No way!
I mean... This sensation is...
I-It's moving!
There's no doubt!
Kazuya...kun?
Ruka-chan!
Are you listening, Kazuya-kun?
Just take her and her boobies for yourself.
Don't, Kazuya-kun.
Isn't Chizuru-san the one you love?
Listen, Kazuya, this won't affect
your booby feelings for her.
If you do another girl,
you don't love her enough?
That's a booby trap.
Every man is like this, my tiddy.
You can make up as many
sexcuses as you want later!
My primal instincts are going wild!
I'll get everything I want if I turn around!
Anything and everything!
Here.
Kazu-chin, you ain't supposed to let
your dick dictate your love life.
Do you remember what I said
back in that hotel room?
I'll have you know I'm
ready to take it all in.
I get it.
I can talk the talk, but I'm
not attractive enough for you.
Ruka-chan?
I'm not mature like Chizuru-san,
and I probably have zero sex appeal.
I'm sure you only see me as some
kid who's trying way too hard.
I know I'm being a bother.
I know I'm probably turning
you off like this.
But...
I can't control myself.
I wanna feel my heart race, too!
Even if you think I'm a pain,
or that I'm too clingy...
Just being with you like this is
making me so happy, I could cry.
"Not attractive enough"? Are you kidding me?!
I wanna make you mine right now!
You're so cute, I'm about
ready to explode over here!
Kazuya...kun?
But I don't think this is love.
I can't lay a hand on you like this!
I can't take that next step!
I would never call you a bother!
Before you, I never had a girl say
she liked me in my entire life...
Deep down, I'm so happy
that I could jump for joy.
I honestly can't believe a girl like
you would ever tell me she likes me.
So please, keep your
distance from me tonight.
I'm this close to making
a terrible mistake...
Roll Roll
Dive
Of all the golden opportunities
to let slip...
Virginity
continues!!
Deep down, I'm so happy
that I could jump for joy.
I honestly can't believe a girl like
you would ever tell me she likes me.
Dazed
Couldn't sleep a wink
You've got some wild bags under your eyes.
Gee, thanks.
When all's said and done, I'm glad
I got through that night unscathed.
Well, we can save the sex for another time.
Wh-What?!
Also, it made me really happy.
I'd always thought you found me a nuisance.
So it felt like you told me
I could stay by your side.
Ruka-chan...
Y-You! What was...
C... Cute!
Huff...
See you, Kazuya-kun! Thank you!
You kindly took the lead and made
it a night I would never forget!
Ichinose
I'll forever remember the
joy I felt last night!
Bye.
Shiver... Shiver...
Ichinose
Tremble
I guess she must still be asleep...
Close shave!
What?!
Thanks for everything last night, Kazuya-kun!
Sure, though it wore me out.
Gee, I wonder what it was that wore you out.
Curious, Chizuru-san?
Do you wanna know all of the love
story we played out in his apartment?!
Not really. I'm just his next-door neighbor.
Mizuhara's being cold!
Too cold! It's giving me brain freeze!
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Birthday...
...and Girlfriend."
Wait, birthday? Whose?!
"Birthday and Girlfriend"
Who knows?
Brr!